{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549184930849","data":{"timestamp":" 1549184930849"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549184935806","data":{"timestamp":" 1549184935806"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549184957106","data":{"timestamp":" 1549184957105"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 791fcf44-3235-4e8f-830a-f508ada68ddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_bwa_cho_chu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549184963746","data":{"timestamp":" 1549184963745"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 791fcf44-3235-4e8f-830a-f508ada68ddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_gha_chi_mli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549184970401","data":{"timestamp":" 1549184970400"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 791fcf44-3235-4e8f-830a-f508ada68ddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_vya_mdo_che"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549184977064","data":{"timestamp":" 1549184977064"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 791fcf44-3235-4e8f-830a-f508ada68ddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mti_mji_mno"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549184983693","data":{"timestamp":" 1549184983692"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 791fcf44-3235-4e8f-830a-f508ada68ddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mlu_mbi_mli"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549184990312","data":{"timestamp":" 1549184990311"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 791fcf44-3235-4e8f-830a-f508ada68ddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ngi_shi_kwe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549184996915","data":{"timestamp":" 1549184996915"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 791fcf44-3235-4e8f-830a-f508ada68ddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_vyi_nji_kwa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185003541","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185003541"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 791fcf44-3235-4e8f-830a-f508ada68ddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nja_sha_mto"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185010197","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185010197"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 791fcf44-3235-4e8f-830a-f508ada68ddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_vyu_mki_nju"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185016864","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185016863"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 791fcf44-3235-4e8f-830a-f508ada68ddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_chi_ndu_ngu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185030017","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185030017"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 791fcf44-3235-4e8f-830a-f508ada68ddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_chi_ndu_ngu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185036376","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185036376"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" b107e40c-7031-4eb1-ba7e-b5f4c16acc63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185048430","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185048429"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" b107e40c-7031-4eb1-ba7e-b5f4c16acc63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185051090","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185051089"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" b107e40c-7031-4eb1-ba7e-b5f4c16acc63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185051255","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185051255"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" b107e40c-7031-4eb1-ba7e-b5f4c16acc63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185066743","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185066743"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185086077","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185086077"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_bwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185087919","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185087918"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_bwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185096136","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185096136"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_bwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185098853","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185098852"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_bwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185101939","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185101939"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_bwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185104455","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185104455"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_bwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185109656","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185109655"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_bwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185124356","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185124356"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mre"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185128148","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185128148"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mre"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185131731","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185131731"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mre"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185153460","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185153460"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_njo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185160834","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185160834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_njo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185167806","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185167805"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_njo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185171354","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185171354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_njo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185177688","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185177688"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_njo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185184817","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185184817"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_njo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185187579","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185187579"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_njo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185201556","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185201556"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185206612","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185206612"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185206712","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185206712"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185215500","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185215499"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185216953","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185216953"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185232426","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185232425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mju"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185241408","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185241408"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mju"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185243800","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185243800"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mju"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185253121","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185253121"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185255240","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185255239"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185257788","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185257788"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185267000","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185267000"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185279318","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185279318"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nje"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185283400","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185283400"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nje"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185287470","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185287470"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nje"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185296733","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185296733"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mjo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185303830","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185303830"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mjo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185308427","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185308427"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mjo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185311299","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185311299"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mjo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185323418","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185323417"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nye"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185325850","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185325849"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nye"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185327976","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185327976"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nye"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185336480","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185336480"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nye"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185338408","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185338407"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nye"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185341216","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185341216"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nye"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185355330","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185355330"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mle"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185358003","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185358003"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mle"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185361092","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185361092"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mle"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185370497","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185370497"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_mle"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185379802","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185379802"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 5dd19a31-26d9-4fbf-9d26-05f8dec75df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mle"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185391601","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185391601"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 08e33c18-0169-4066-b9ab-8a70b6d6c3c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mfa_sho-mko-mfa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mfa"," userResponse":" mko"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185396976","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185396976"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 08e33c18-0169-4066-b9ab-8a70b6d6c3c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mfa_sho-mko-mfa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mfa"," userResponse":" mfa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185401863","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185401863"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 08e33c18-0169-4066-b9ab-8a70b6d6c3c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nya_shu-nya-mki"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nya"," userResponse":" nya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185406459","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185406459"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 08e33c18-0169-4066-b9ab-8a70b6d6c3c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mdo_mka-mdo-nde"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mdo"," userResponse":" mdo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185411371","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185411370"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 08e33c18-0169-4066-b9ab-8a70b6d6c3c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sha_sha-tha-nde"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sha"," userResponse":" sha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185420339","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185420339"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 08e33c18-0169-4066-b9ab-8a70b6d6c3c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyu_nje-nyu-bwe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyu"," userResponse":" nyu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185425545","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185425544"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 08e33c18-0169-4066-b9ab-8a70b6d6c3c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mla_mfu-mwa-mla"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mla"," userResponse":" mla"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185429857","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185429857"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 08e33c18-0169-4066-b9ab-8a70b6d6c3c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_twi_twi-mza-twa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" twi"," userResponse":" twi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185434659","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185434659"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 08e33c18-0169-4066-b9ab-8a70b6d6c3c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bwa_ngi-bwa-tha"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bwa"," userResponse":" bwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185439348","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185439348"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 08e33c18-0169-4066-b9ab-8a70b6d6c3c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_nja-nye-nga"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185444011","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185444011"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 08e33c18-0169-4066-b9ab-8a70b6d6c3c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_ngo-mme-mba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185449769","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185449768"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 08e33c18-0169-4066-b9ab-8a70b6d6c3c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_ngo-mme-mba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185487791","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185487791"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 08e33c18-0169-4066-b9ab-8a70b6d6c3c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_ngo-mme-mba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185500111","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185500111"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" f06ec4cc-0c43-4b71-bb95-0d93bc8fd003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nji_mzi-nji-mre"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nji"," userResponse":" nji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185512878","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185512878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" f06ec4cc-0c43-4b71-bb95-0d93bc8fd003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mki_bwa-mki-mpe"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mki"," userResponse":" mki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185519361","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185519360"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" f06ec4cc-0c43-4b71-bb95-0d93bc8fd003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mna_kha-mna-bwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mna"," userResponse":" mna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185523940","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185523940"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" f06ec4cc-0c43-4b71-bb95-0d93bc8fd003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sho_mgu-sho-nji"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sho"," userResponse":" sho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185529532","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185529531"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" f06ec4cc-0c43-4b71-bb95-0d93bc8fd003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nge_vya-nge-dha"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nge"," userResponse":" nge"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185535052","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185535052"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" f06ec4cc-0c43-4b71-bb95-0d93bc8fd003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bwa_ndi-msa-bwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bwa"," userResponse":" bwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185540110","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185540110"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" f06ec4cc-0c43-4b71-bb95-0d93bc8fd003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbu_kha-mbu-twe"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbu"," userResponse":" mbu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185544766","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185544766"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" f06ec4cc-0c43-4b71-bb95-0d93bc8fd003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_twe_nja-dha-twe"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" twe"," userResponse":" twe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185549509","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185549508"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" f06ec4cc-0c43-4b71-bb95-0d93bc8fd003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_she_ndo-nda-she"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" she"," userResponse":" she"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185554455","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185554455"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" f06ec4cc-0c43-4b71-bb95-0d93bc8fd003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwi_mwi-ngi-mzu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwi"," userResponse":" mwi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185560216","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185560216"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" f06ec4cc-0c43-4b71-bb95-0d93bc8fd003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mwi_mwi-ngi-mzu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185566965","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185566965"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" f06ec4cc-0c43-4b71-bb95-0d93bc8fd003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mwi_mwi-ngi-mzu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185578097","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185578097"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185579395","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185579395"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185585697","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185585696"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185589883","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185589883"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185591361","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185591361"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185593250","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185593249"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185593692","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185593691"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185594182","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185594181"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185594837","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185594837"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185597533","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185597533"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185597687","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185597687"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185598407","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185598407"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185598621","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185598621"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185600322","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185600322"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185603858","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185603858"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185605672","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185605671"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185605773","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185605772"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185606641","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185606640"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185607069","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185607069"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185607907","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185607907"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185611787","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185611787"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWEYU"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185614698","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185614698"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWEYU"," userResponse":" KWEYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185620997","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185620997"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AMEVALIA"," userResponse":" START_AMEVALIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185621859","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185621858"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AMEVALIA"," userResponse":" START_AMEVALIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185623806","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185623805"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEVALIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185626049","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185626048"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185626681","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185626680"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185627371","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185627370"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185631845","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185631845"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185633659","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185633658"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWEYU"," userResponse":" KWEYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185634715","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185634715"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEVALIA"," userResponse":" AMEVALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185635425","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185635424"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185635624","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185635624"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185636208","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185636207"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185637009","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185637009"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185639084","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185639084"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185642468","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185642468"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185644299","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185644298"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185646029","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185646028"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185648837","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185648836"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" PILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185649923","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185649923"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185649929","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185649929"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185650049","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185650049"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185651873","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185651872"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185651979","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185651978"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185652755","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185652755"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" PILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185653277","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185653276"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185653480","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185653479"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185654164","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185654163"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185657762","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185657762"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" START_HILI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185660846","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185660846"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185661830","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185661829"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185662961","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185662961"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185664594","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185664593"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185664822","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185664822"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185665537","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185665536"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185669897","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185669896"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185670373","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185670373"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185671597","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185671596"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185672078","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185672078"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185676180","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185676180"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185677961","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185677960"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185678078","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185678077"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185678772","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185678771"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185679261","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185679261"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185680081","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185680080"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185686721","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185686721"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185688509","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185688508"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINGU"," userResponse":" PINGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185690020","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185690020"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINA"," userResponse":" LINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185690035","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185690035"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185690916","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185690915"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185691403","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185691402"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" START_MANJANO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185693332","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185693332"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185695051","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185695051"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185696963","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185696962"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185697603","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185697603"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINGU"," userResponse":" PINGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185698347","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185698346"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINA"," userResponse":" LINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185699070","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185699070"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185699205","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185699205"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185700048","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185700048"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549185700336","data":{"timestamp":" 1549185700336"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_120836"," gameId":" 25bbbba8-416a-47f1-8ca5-e5eedda1f461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}